SIVAKUMAR

SAP FICO CONSULTANT, SENIOR CONSULTANT

PHONE I (+91) 9885628605

EMAIL I siva.ficolll@gmail.com

LOCATION I Bengaluru, INDIA

EXPERIENCE I 8 Years 0 Month

Key Skills

- SAP FI
- SAP FICO
- FI-AR
- Co
- Ap
- Asset Accounting
- Internal Orders
- Cost Center Accounting
- New GI
- Fiori Application
- Banking

Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Tamil
- Kannada
- Telugu

Profile Summary

? Having 8 years of Total experience out of 6 years of experience as SAP FI/CO consultant. 2 Implementation and 5 Support Projects Experience in FI &Co Module. ? Proficient in designing and configuration of FI/CO sub modules, General Ledger (FI-GL), Account payable (FI-AP), Account Receivable (FI-AR), and Asset accounting. ? Experience in FI-MM integration (P2P). ? Experience in data migration to move from legacy system to SAP for General ledger Ledger Accounts, Vendor Accounts, and Customer masters using LSMW ? Knowledge in FI-SD integration (OTC) New General ledger (Document Splitting)

Work Experience

SAP FICO consultant, senior Consultant Cognizant 12/2023 - 05/2024

??? Provide status updates in daily/weekly conference calls ??? Understanding the business requirement of the organization ??? Sort out day to day queries of end users. ??? Capacity to perform multiple tasks and deal with different expectations and undertakings simultaneously ??? Understand the process for which a test script is created. ??? Solving of maintenance Issues in the area of General Ledger, Account Payables, Account Receivables. ??? Support to Master data for General Ledger, AP, AR and Bank Master Data ??? Automatic payment run F110 training to users, Configuration of special GL indicators ??? Other support services include -

Configuration with Change Request, Testing of transactions, scenarios and solving transactional issues ??? To support the end users in the areas of FI- GL, AR, ok AP, and Z business process by resolving the day-to-day problems. ??? Fixing the bugs through CR (Changes request) ??? Given KT concepts wise to associate consultants ??? Helping associate consultants to resolve the tickets on time.

Senior Associate

Acuiti labs 04/2023 - 08/2023

??? Provide status updates in daily/weekly conference calls ??? Understanding the business requirement of the organization ??? Validate the reports requirements ??? Validate any changes in customize. ??? Provide training to end-user. ??? Sort out day to day gueries of end users. ??? Enhancement of the SAP for end user based on requirement. ??? Functional testing and Integration Testing. ??? Configure Global settings and Enterprise structure settings. ??? Configure G/L, A/P, A/R, Banking, Interfaces, FI-MM, and FI-SD. ??? Prepare End user training Document. ??? Involvement with FI integration focuses on other SAP-based ERP modules like MM. SD. ??? Least of 5 years of involvement with a full cycle implementation as well as in support projects.

DC Consultant

Deloitte 11/2021 - 02/2023

? Dealing with Medium and Low-Level issues? To support the end users in the areas of FI-GL, AR, AP, by resolving the day-to-day problem? Validations & Substitutions.? Understanding the business requirement of the organization? Preparation of Blue print for implementing the project.? Implementation of the project.? Validate the reports requirements? Validate any changes in customize.? Provide training to end-user.? Sort out day to day queries of end users.? Enhancement of the SAP for end user based

on requirement. ? Prepare Test Scripts. ? Validate Existing Test Scripts. ? Understand the process for which a test script is created. ? Create test data basing on the test script specifications. ? Document the test results.

Associate Consultant

Mesprosoft 08/2018 - 05/2021

??? Resolving the priority tickets as per SLA (Service Level Agreement) ??? Supporting to end users in Day to day transactions, Month end and Year end activities ??? Providing immediate solutions to client/end user based on the requirement of the issues ??? Discussing and understanding about the new requirement raised by business users and providing solution ??? Solving of maintenance Issues in the area of General Ledger, Account Payables, Account Receivables, Asset Accounting, House bank and Tax reports ??? Support to Master data for General Ledger, Asset and Bank Master Data ??? Automatic payment run F110 training to users, Configuration of special GL indicators ??? Configuration of Depreciation keys, screen layout for asset master data screen layout for asset depreciation area ??? Other support services include - Configuration with Change Request, Testing of transactions, scenarios and solving transactional issues ??? To support the end users in the areas of FI- GL, AR, AP, AA, BK and CO-CEA,CCA, IO,FSV and Z business process by resolving the day-to-day problems ??? To resolve the issue bank statement FEBAN ??? To resolve the legal report issues like Tax report ??? Fixing the bugs through CR (Changes request) ??? Given KT concepts wise to associate consultants ??? Helping associate consultants to resolve the tickets on time

Process Associate
Dhanu adds
01/2015 - 12/2016

Education

Integrated PG - Management

2023

NO

B.Com - Commerce 2014

monad university

Grade - 70%

10th

2007

Andhra Pradesh , English Grade - 65-69.9%